Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Iconographic Collection, 1848-2005 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Officers and Staff Photographs, 1848-1998 and undated, (18 boxes)
  - Harmon, Sigurd (see Strouse, Norman) (Box OS4)
  - Harris, Harold, undated (Box OS4)
  - Hauptfuhrer, Barbara Barnes, undated (Box OS4)
  - Hayes, Evangeline (Vangie), 1980 (Box OS4)
  - Hayres, Ed, 1989 (Box OS4)
  - Hebert, Jacques, circa 1980s (Box OS4)
  - Henderson, Howard (see also: Officers: U.S.: New York Office: Clients), circa 1943 (Box OS5)
  - Hermann, Denise, 1969 (Box OS5)
  - Hester, James M., 1969 (Box OS5)
  - Hicks, Wyatte E., circa 1960-1973 (Box OS5)
  - Hieber, Denise, undated (Box OS5)
  - Hielscher, Bob, undated (Box OS5)
  - Hiltebrand, Ernest, 1971 (Box OS5)
  - Hinks, Ken (see also: Strouse, Norman), undated (Box OS5)
  - Hinks, W. Kennett (see also: Corporate Events: Retired Board of Directors Dinner; Wilson, Edward G.), circa 1930-1976 (Box OS5)
  - Hinks, William (see also: Meek, Samuel), 1960, 1967 (Box OS5)
  - Hoffmann, Hans (see also: Seymour, Dan), 1964, 1968 (Box OS5)
  - Holden, Pauline, 1969 (Box OS5)
  - Holden, Win, 1964 (Box OS5)
  - Hollander, Peter A.E., 1968 (Box OS5)
  - Holmes, John, circa 1980s (Box OS5)
  - Holodnicki, Steve, 1977 (Box OS5)
  - Holt, Stanley, circa 1931 (Box OS5)
  - Hontiveras, Lenny (Leon T.), circa 1980s (Box OS5)
  - Hopps, Oliver, circa 1957 (Box OS5)
  - Horak, Peter, circa 1980s (Box OS5)
  - Howarth, Ross, circa 1981 (Box OS5)
  - Howington, Marion, undated (Box OS5)
  - Howington, Marion, 1975-1976 (Box OS5)
  - Humphries, John, circa 1968 (Box OS5)
  - Hurd, Richard, circa 1979 (Box OS5)
  - Hylan, William H., circa 1965 (Box OS5)
  - Ibuki, T. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS5)
  - Irvine, Robert, 1975-1976 (Box OS5)
  - Ishihara, Y. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS5)
  - Ivie, Constance B., circa 1970-1979 (Box OS5)
  - Jaccaci, Thayer, 1950s-1960s (Box OS5)
  - Jaccoma, George, undated (Box OS5)
  - Jaccoma, George, 1980 (Box OS5)
  - Jacklin, Paul, 1978 (Box OS5)
  - Jackson, Babette, 1979 (Box OS5)
  - Jackson, Henry, 1960 (Box OS5)
  - Jackson, Henry, 1950s (Box OS5)
  - James, David (see also: Saunders, Douglas), circa 1955 (Box OS5)
  - Jansen, Hermine, 1969 (Box OS5)
  - Jardine, Theodore P., circa 1950s-1966 (Box OS5)
  - Jeanty, Paul, 1970s (Box OS5)
  - Johnson, Arno, circa 1950s-1968 (Box OS5)
  - Johnson, Frank, 1960s (Box OS5)
  - Johnston, Donald G. (Don) (See also Oversize; Doyer, Robert; Parrild, Sven; Offices: New York: events; Offices: U.S.: New York; Meek, Samuel; Woodell, Shirley), 1931-1986, (1-10 of 16 folders) (Box OS5)
  - Johnston, Donald G. (Don) (continued), 1931-1986, (11-16 of 16 folders) (Box OS6)
  - Johnston, Sarita (see Johnston, G. Donald) (Box OS7)
  - Jones, Alun H., circa 1976-1980 (Box OS7)
  - Jones, Chris, undated (Box OS7)
  - Jones, Robert, 1967, 1970s (Box OS7)
  - Joyce, Timothy, circa 1979 (Box OS7)
  - Jubien, Arthur, circa 1969 (Box OS7)
  - Kaiser, Laura, 1977 (Box OS7)
  - Kale, Diane, undated (Box OS7)
  - Kang, Sungman, circa 1980s (Box OS7)
  - Karnig, Andrew, 1967 (Box OS7)
  - Karp, Ruth Downing, 1969 (Box OS7)
  - Keane, John. G, 1968 (Box OS7)
  - Keating, Edward, 1970s (Box OS7)
  - Keating, Marianne, 1964 (Box OS7)
  - Keithly, James, 1950s-1980s (Box OS7)
  - Kelliher, Steve, 1973 (Box OS7)
  - Kemp, Herbert, circa 1976-1982 (Box OS7)
  - Kennedy, James W., 1980 (Box OS7)
  - Kenyon, Robert E. Jr. (see Strouse, Norman) (Box OS7)
  - Kerasiotis, Chris, circa 1980s (Box OS7)
  - Keough, Bill, undated (Box OS7)
  - Khanna, Mike, circa 1980s (Box OS7)
  - Khusro, Iftekhar A. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS7)
  - Kim, Peter (see Patterson, James), 1991 (Box OS7)
  - King, Margaret (Peggy), 1950s-1960s (Box OS7)
  - King, Robert, 1979 (Box OS7)
  - King, Stephen, 1986 (Box OS7)
  - Kinney, Gilbert, circa 1940s (Box OS7)
  - Kirchner, Donald P., circa 1960s (Box OS7)
  - Kittel, Fred, circa 1970s (Box OS7)
  - Kobayshi, K. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS7)
  - Koelle, John R., 1977 (Box OS7)
  - Kohl, Howard, circa 1960s (Box OS7)
  - Komives, Mike, 1977 (Box OS7)
  - Kovas, Ron, circa 1979, 1985 (Box OS7)
  - Kovas, Ron, 1976 (Box OS7)
  - Kramer, Marc (see Strouse, Norman) (Box OS7)
  - Kreiger, Bud (see Strouse, Norman) (Box OS7)
  - Krishnamoorthy, K.S. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS7)
  - Krupski, A., circa 1980s (Box OS7)
  - Kurek, Ralph, 1975 (Box OS7)
  - Kuykendall, Ron, 1977-1978 (Box OS7)
  - Lane, Bill, undated (Box OS7)
  - Lanigan, Denis, circa 1961-1985 (Box OS7)
  - Lanigan, Jean Sanderson (see Sanderson, Jean) (Box OS7)
  - Lapardo, Pat, 1961 (Box OS7)
  - Laurie, William D., circa 1964 (Box OS7)
  - Lavely, Anthony, 1976 (Box OS7)
  - Leach, Owen G., 1973 (Box OS7)
  - League, Raymond, circa 1966 (Box OS7)
  - Leal, Roberto, circa 1980s (Box OS7)
  - Lee, Harry A. (see also: Meek, Samuel), circa 1955-1970s (Box OS7)
  - Lehner, Paul, 1964 (Box OS7)
  - Lemon, Luther Orange, circa 1965 (Box OS7)
  - Lepage, Robert, circa 1950 (Box OS7)
  - Lihoregu, Herve, circa 1980s (Box OS7)
  - Linder, Frank, 1958 (Box OS7)
  - Lindesay-Bethune, John, 1965-1980 (Box OS7)
  - Littig, Ross, undated (Box OS7)
  - Little, Lyle (see also: Meek, Samuel; Wilson, Edward G.), 1950-1970s (Box OS7)
  - Loarie, Willard J., circa 1950s (Box OS7)
  - Lollis, Mike, 1976 (Box OS7)
  - Lord, Dick (see Wilson, Edward B.) (Box OS7)
  - Lord, Walter, undated (Box OS7)
  - Luisi, Marie, 1960s-1977 (Box OS7)
  - Lund, Clarence S., circa 1960s (Box OS7)
  - Lundin, Robert, undated (Box OS7)
  - Lyman, William (see Johnson, Frank) (Box OS7)
  - Lynch, William, circa 1973 (Box OS7)
  - Lyons, Martin, 1979 (Box OS7)
  - Mabley, Thomas, circa 1970s (Box OS7)
  - Macedo, Richard, circa 1977 (Box OS7)
  - Mackey, Peter, circa 1995 (Box OS7)
  - MacMaster, Norman, circa 1980s (Box OS7)
  - Magine, John, 1976 (Box OS7)
  - Maher, John, 1979 (Box OS7)
  - Maheux, Denise, circa 1969 (Box OS7)
  - Mahmood, A. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS7)
  - Mainero, Frank, circa 1979 (Box OS7)
  - Malizia, Denise, 1975 (Box OS7)
  - Manning, Burt (see also: New York: Events: Party: Christmas; New York Office: Clients: STP; New York Office: Events: Awards; New York: Events: Office Rally; New York: Events: Intra-Office Move; New York: Events: Outing: Boat ride; Offices: U.S.: New York; Offices: USA: New York: Clients: BK; Obrien Walter), 1966-1990, (3 folders) (Box OS7)
  - Marans, David, early 1990s (Box OS7)
  - Markman, Ken, 1984 (Box OS7)
  - Marshall, Dan, circa 1967 (Box OS7)
  - Martell, Charles, undated (Box OS7)
  - Martell, Charles, 1970 (Box OS7)
  - Martello, Frank T., 1979 (Box OS7)
  - Marti-Coll, Enrique, 1986 (Box OS7)
  - Materan, David, circa 1985 (Box OS7)
  - Mavros, Dimitri, circa 1980s (Box OS7)
  - May, David, 1995 (Box OS8)
  - May, Michael, 1973 (Box OS8)
  - McCallin, Edward Jr., 1980 (Box OS8)
  - McCart, Dennis, 1982 (Box OS8)
  - McClowry, Bob, early 1990s (Box OS8)
  - McCombs, Ed, 1978 (Box OS8)
  - McCrey, Joel (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS8)
  - McEnroe, Tim, 1974 (Box OS8)
  - McIntee, Stanley, 1984 (Box OS8)
  - McIntyre, Robert, undated (Box OS8)
  - McKee, Ruyard C., 1968 (Box OS8)
  - McKeeham, William C., circa 1950 (Box OS8)
  - McKenna, Dorothy, 1979 (Box OS8)
  - McLaughlin, Bill, undated (Box OS8)
  - McMahon, Doug, early 1990s (Box OS8)
  - McQuigg, John, 1960-1969 (Box OS8)
  - Meads, Walter (Chip) F., 1964-1966 (Box OS8)
  - Mear, David, 1990s (Box OS8)
  - Meek, Priscilla (see also: Meek, Sam), undated (Box OS8)
  - Meek, Samuel W. (see also: Resor, Stanley; Wilson, E.G.), 1925-1986, (6 folders) (Box OS8)
  - Melton, James (see Strouse, Norman) (Box OS8)
  - Merrick, Robert F. (see also: Resor, Stanley), circa 1960-1961 (Box OS9)
  - Metter, Bert, 1980 (Box OS9)
  - Meyers, Farlan, 1968 Dec 6 (Box OS9)
  - Middleton, Alan, 1985 (Box OS9)
  - Millar, A. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS9)
  - Miller, Madeleine, 1990s (Box OS9)
  - Milliken, Cynthia, undated (Box OS9)
  - Mills, Peter, 1979 (Box OS9)
  - Minhas, I. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS9)
  - Mitchell-Innes, Alexander P., 1967 (Box OS9)
  - Miyahara, Y. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS9)
  - Mizuno, S. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS9)
  - Modisett, John, 1966 (Box OS9)
  - Moloney, E.J., circa 1930s (Box OS9)
  - Monsarrat, John (see also: Offices: USA: Chicago: Client), 1966-1968 (Box OS9)
  - Moodie, John, 1970 (Box OS9)
  - Moran, H.J., 1970 (Box OS9)
  - Moran, Patrick E., 1980 (Box OS9)
  - Mori, Saburo (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS9)
  - Morrison, Julian, undated (Box OS9)
  - Mortola, Manuel (see also: Wilson, Edward G.), circa 1969 (Box OS9)
  - Moss, Larry, 1974 (Box OS9)
  - Mrugal, Fran, undated (Box OS9)
  - Mueller, Andy, undated (Box OS9)
  - Mueller, Gary, 1978 (Box OS9)
  - Muldoon, William, undated (Box OS9)
  - Muller, Jan, 1973-1974 (Box OS9)
  - Muller, Marty, late 1980s (Box OS9)
  - Murray, Jane Ellen, 1960s, 1978 (Box OS9)
  - Myers, Farlan, 1968 (Box OS9)
  - Mygatt, Philip, 1966 (Box OS9)
  - Nagrajan, T.S. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS9)
  - Nair, S.M. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS9)
  - Nakayama, Jiro (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS9)
  - Napier, Mark, circa 1955-1970s (Box OS9)
  - Naples, Mike (see also: Bartos, Rena), 1982 (Box OS9)
  - Neith, J.R. (see Meek Samuel) (Box OS9)
  - Nelson, Linnea, circa 1960 (Box OS9)
  - Newman, Hildie, undated (Box OS9)
  - Nickles, Liz, 1978 (Box OS9)
  - Nieman, Han, 1987 (Box OS9)
  - Nishimura, T. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS9)
  - Norsworthy, Bob, circa 1950s (Box OS9)
  - Nykopp, Johan (see Meek, Samuel) (Box OS9)
  - Oates, James F. Jr. (see Strouse, Norman) (Box OS9)
  - O'Brien, Patrick E., undated (Box OS9)
  - O'Brien, Wally, age 4, 1979-1985 (Box OS9)
  - O'Brien, Walter J., 1980s (Box OS9)
  - Obrzut, Greg, 1969, 1975 (Box OS9)
  - O'Connell, Tom, undated (Box OS9)
  - Odell, Norman C., 1965 (Box OS9)
  - Odishoo, Dan, 1973, 1976 (Box OS9)
  - Odom, Edward J., 1976 (Box OS9)
  - O'Donnell, Joe (see also: Johnston, G. Donald), 1981-1986 (Box OS9)
  - O'Donnell, William S., 1967 (Box OS9)
  - O'Grady, Thomas F., circa 1967 (Box OS9)
  - Oldland, John, 1980 (Box OS9)
  - Olshan, Larry, circa 1980 (Box OS9)
  - Olson, Sidney A., circa 1956-1964 (Box OS9)
  - O'Meara, Walter, circa 1940s (Box OS9)
  - Orfuss, Mitchell, 1990s (Box OS9)
  - Orsi, Jose Roberto (see also: Offices: Brazil: Rio de Janeiro: Group Portraits), circa 1978 (Box OS9)
  - Ostrofe, Allen, undated (Box OS9)
  - Ostrom, Doris, 1965, Dec. (Box OS9)
  - Otero, Fernando, 1985 (Box OS9)
  - Overaker, John (see also: Jones, Robert), 1978 (Box OS9)
  - Owett, Bernie, undated (Box OS9)
  - Owett, Bernie (see also Oversize), 1954-1979, (2 folders) (Box OS9)
  - Owett, Trudy, 1965 (Box OS9)
  - Padmoubhan, N. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS9)
  - Page, J. Hutcheson, circa 1950-1962 (Box OS9)
  - Paine, Thos, undated (Box OS9)
  - Palen, Gilbert, 1962-1970s (Box OS9)
  - Palen, Gilbert and Blackman, Elizabeth, 1964 (Box OS9)
  - Palmer, Jeff, 1977 (Box OS9)
  - Palmer, William G., circa 1930 (Box OS9)
  - Pandiani, Wilma Vigano, circa 1985 (Box OS9)
  - Paniguian, Hracia, circa 1953 (Box OS9)
  - Parker, Austin (Ace), 1972 (Box OS9)
  - Parker, Joan, undated (Box OS9)
  - Parrild, Sven (see also: Sutton, Tom; Ulrich, Einer), 1960-1972 (Box OS9)
  - Patterson, James, 1984, 1985 (Box OS9)
  - Patterson, James, 1991-1992 (Box OS9)
  - Patterson, James, 1989 Mar. (Box OS9)
  - Patterson, James, undated (Box OS9)
  - Patterson, Robert (see Meek, Samuel) (Box OS9)
  - Pavao, Lee, 1984 (Box OS10)
  - Paxton, Mickey, circa 1995 (Box OS10)
  - Pearlman, Stuart, 1992 (Box OS10)
  - Peirce, Evelyn, circa 1950-1965 (Box OS10)
  - Peniche, William M., 1979 (Box OS10)
  - Peniche, William M. (Bill), 1975 (Box OS10)
  - Perdono, Luis, 1972 (Box OS10)
  - Perez, Domingo, circa 1992 (Box OS10)
  - Peters, John E., circa 1979, 1985 (Box OS10)
  - Peterson, B., 1981 (Box OS10)
  - Pflager, Gus, undated (Box OS10)
  - Pfouts, Barry, 1976 (Box OS10)
  - Pierce, Russell, 1930s, 1980s (Box OS10)
  - Pierce, Thurman, undated (Box OS10)
  - Pilling, J Ross, Jr., 1965 (Box OS10)
  - Pollet, Richard, undated (Box OS10)
  - Pool, Jean, 1992 (Box OS10)
  - Pope, Wendell, 1974 (Box OS10)
  - Popper, Robert, undated (Box OS10)
  - Popper, Susan, 1990s (Box OS10)
  - Potter, Carol, circa mid 1990s (Box OS10)
  - Praetorius, William A., 1973 (Box OS10)
  - Preschel, Lee, undated (Box OS10)
  - Preschel, W. Lee, 1974-1985 (Box OS10)
  - Preston, Marion, 1960-1978 (Box OS10)
  - PreuB, Werner, circa 1980s (Box OS10)
  - Proctor, Page, 1978 (Box OS10)
  - Psaltis, Michael, undated (Box OS10)
  - Punthakey, F.H. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS10)
  - Qamari, T.A. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS10)
  - Raj, Dhan (see also: Meek, Samuel), circa 1965 (Box OS10)
  - Ramaswami, V. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS10)
  - Rangathan, R. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS10)
  - Rasor, Richard, circa 1976 (Box OS10)
  - Rather, Dan (see Johnston, G. Donald (Don)) (Box OS10)
  - Raymond, Charles, circa 1900s (Box OS10)
  - Reber, John U. (see also Oversize), circa 1930s (Box OS10)
  - Reed, Ruth (see Reed, Vergil) (Box OS10)
  - Reed, Vergil D., 1946-1958 (Box OS10)
  - Reeves, George C. (see also: Young, James Webb), circa 1960s (Box OS10)
  - Resor, Helen Landsdowne (see also: Young, James Webb), circa 1917-1961 (Box OS11)
  - Resor, Stanley Burnet (see also Oversize; Meek, Samuel; Offices: Brazil: São Paulo; Young, James Webb), 1901-1964, (13 folders) (Box OS11)
  - Restall, Robin, undated (Box OS12)
  - Rex, Harriet Feeney, circa 1945-1970 (Box OS12)
  - Reynolds, Neil, 1978 (Box OS12)
  - Rheinstrom, Charles A., circa 1950s (Box OS12)
  - Richardson, George P., 1929-1930 (Box OS12)
  - Ridley, Helen Friedburg, undated (Box OS12)
  - Robbins, Ken, circa 1970s (Box OS12)
  - Robertson, Don, circa 1970s (Box OS12)
  - Robertson, Donald C., 1980 (Box OS12)
  - Rockwell, Norman (see Elton, Wallace) (Box OS12)
  - Rodgers, John (see Resor, Stanley) (Box OS12)
  - Ross, William, circa 1970s (Box OS12)
  - Rubinick, Walter R., 1975 (Box OS12)
  - Rudolph, Peter, circa 1980s (Box OS12)
  - Ruiz, Tony, undated (Box OS12)
  - Ruppen, Frank, 1993 (Box OS12)
  - Russell, J. Hamilton, undated (Box OS12)
  - Russo, John (see Resor, Stanley) (Box OS12)
  - Ryan, O'Neill, 1965 (Box OS12)
  - Rydholm, Ralph, undated (Box OS12)
  - Rydholm, Ralph, 1976 (Box OS12)
  - Ryman, Tina, 1978 (Box OS12)
  - Saillard, Marc, circa 1980s (Box OS12)
  - Saito, Kinichiro (see also: Offices: Japan: Tokyo: Group), 1958-1973 (Box OS12)
  - Sanderson, Jean, 1951 (Box OS12)
  - Sanderson, Jean (see also: Campbell-Harris, David), 1951 (Box OS12)
  - Sargeant, Neville, 1980 (Box OS12)
  - Saunders, Douglas, circa 1950s (Box OS12)
  - Saxon, Joyce, pre-1983 (Box OS12)
  - Schachte, Henry F., 1969, 1978 (Box OS12)
  - Schirmacher, Alice (Nena), 1961 (Box OS12)
  - Schjaerven, Stein, circa 1985 (Box OS12)
  - Schulte, Joseph, 1983 (Box OS12)
  - Schulte, Theodore (see Johnson, Frank) (Box OS12)
  - Schutzer, Hilda Ulbrich, 1969 (Box OS12)
  - Schwarz, Burkhard, circa 1980s (Box OS12)
  - Schweitzer, Peter, circa 1960s (Box OS12)
  - Schweitzer, Peter, 1989 (Box OS12)
  - Schweitzer, Peter, 1990s-1998 (Box OS12)
  - Scollay, Jack, circa 1980-1986 (Box OS12)
  - Scollay, John, 1977-1978 (Box OS12)
  - Scott, Derry (see Meek, Samuel) (Box OS12)
  - Scott, Robert, 1980 (Box OS12)
  - Scotti, Anna, 1969 (Box OS12)
  - Secunda, Eugene (see also: Wilson, Edward B.), 1979 (Box OS12)
  - Secunda, Gene, undated (Box OS12)
  - Sedgwick, Ursula, 1969 (Box OS12)
  - Seeler, Richard W. (see Strouse, Norman) (Box OS12)
  - Seibert, Wilson (Bill), 1980 (Box OS12)
  - Seisser, Todd, circa 1996 (Box OS12)
  - Selson, Aimella, 1967 (Box OS12)
  - Senior, Raimond, circa 1940s-1966 (Box OS12)
  - Seymour, Dan (see also Oversize; Doyer, Robert; Parrild, Sven; Strouse, Norman), circa 1940s-1968, (8 folders) (Box OS12)
  - Shakur, A. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS12)
  - Sharfman, Bill, circa 1980-1985 (Box OS12)
  - Sharman, John, 1960-1983 (Box OS12)
  - Sharman, Ron (see also: Offices: USA: New York: Clients), 1970-1980 (Box OS12)
  - Shea, Bill, circa 1996 (Box OS12)
  - Sherman, Jeff, 1978 (Box OS12)
  - Sherwood, Edwin, 1971 (Box OS12)
  - Siegal, Audrey, 1996 (Box OS12)
  - Simonin, Dominique, undated (Box OS12)
  - Simonson, Carl W., undated (Box OS12)
  - Simpson, David, 1980s-1997 (Box OS12)
  - Simpson, Jean, circa 1960s (Box OS13)
  - Sinclair, Andrew, circa 1960s (Box OS13)
  - Sisbro, Mogens, 1975 (Box OS13)
  - Sitts, Brian, 1993 (Box OS13)
  - Skinner, Mark, 1985 (Box OS13)
  - Smith, Francis, circa 1957 (Box OS13)
  - Smith, Kenneth, 1979 (Box OS13)
  - Smith, Quentin I. Jr., circa 1975-1980 (Box OS13)
  - Smith, Rae, circa 1938 (Box OS13)
  - Snowday, Jane Collins, 1971-1978 (Box OS13)
  - Snowdon, Lord (see Oversize; Seymour, Dan; Strouse, Norman) (Box OS13)
  - Snyder, Eric, 1990s (Box OS13)
  - Sommerville, Larry (see McCombs, Ed), 1978 (Box OS13)
  - Soskin, David H., circa 1985-1987 (Box OS13)
  - Souhami, Gerard (see also: Seymour, Dan), 1967-1968 (Box OS13)
  - Sparkman, David, circa 1988 (Box OS13)
  - Speyer, George W., 1930 (Box OS13)
  - Spivak, Helayne, 1996 (Box OS13)
  - Stansbury, Harold, circa 1949 (Box OS13)
  - Stanton, Henry, 1944 (Box OS13)
  - Starr, Henry, circa 1950 (Box OS13)
  - Stephenson, Nancy F., circa 1950s (Box OS13)
  - Stevens, Henry M., 1950 (Box OS13)
  - Stevens, Jack, 1977 (Box OS13)
  - Stimson, Paul, 1980 (Box OS13)
  - Stiver, Micheal (see Resor, Stanley) (Box OS13)
  - Stobbs, Barry, 1978 (Box OS13)
  - Stridsberg, Albert, 1966 (Box OS13)
  - Strouse, Charlotte (see also: Strouse, Norman), undated (Box OS14)
  - Strouse, Norman (see also Oversize; Keating, Marianne; Parrild, Sven; Resor, Stanley; Seymour, Dan; US: New York: Clients: World's Fair; Offices: US: Detroit: Events; Offices: US: New York: Clients; Ulrich, Einer), 1923-1986 and undated, (42 folders) (Box OS14)
  - Styles, Stacey, 1996 (Box OS15)
  - Sullivan, Donald G., circa 1985 (Box OS15)
  - Sullivan, Malcolm, 1970s, 1980s (Box OS15)
  - Sutton, Thomas (see also Oversize; Johnston, G. Donald; Offices: US: Japan: Tokyo: Group: Portraits; Parrild, Sven; Seymour, Dan), 1953-1970s, (6 folders) (Box OS15)
  - Swamindhan, Nuru, circa 1969 (Box OS15)
  - Swamy, R.K. (see also: Wilson, Edward G.), circa 1950 (Box OS15)
  - Tagoada, Miguel Garcia, 1985 (Box OS15)
  - Taubin, Bill (see Jaccoma, George), 1980 (Box OS15)
  - Taylor, Gordon, circa 1985 (Box OS15)
  - Taylor, Tom, undated (Box OS15)
  - Taylor, William C., undated (Box OS15)
  - Telser, Eugene, 1972 (Box OS15)
  - Tessier, Alain, 1978 (Box OS15)
  - Thomas, Allen, 1982, (2 folders) (Box OS15)
  - Thompson, Donald (see also: Offices: Philippines: Manila: Events), 1965-1985 (Box OS15)
  - Thompson, James Walter (See also Oversize), circa 1848-1920, (11 folders) (Box OS16)
  - Thompson, William Charles, undated (Box OS17)
  - Thomson, Dick, 1967 (Box OS17)
  - Thorburn, Donaldson B., 1959, 1964 (Box OS17)
  - Thun, Ferdinand (see Strouse, Norman) (Box OS17)
  - Tiggelman, Adriaan, 1984 (Box OS17)
  - Tolstoi, Anne (see Foster, Anne Tolstoi) (Box OS17)
  - Treacy, Jacqueline, 1976 (Box OS17)
  - Treasure, John A., 1950s-1970 (Box OS17)
  - Trencher, Lewis J., 1995 (Box OS17)
  - Tripp, Granger, circa 1970s (Box OS17)
  - Tripp, Marian, circa 1972 (Box OS17)
  - Trokenheim, Abe, 1982 (Box OS17)
  - Trovati, Vince, 1987 (Box OS17)
  - Trzuskowski, John (w/ proofs), 1980 (Box OS17)
  - Tuggleman, Adriaan, 1984 (Box OS17)
  - Uihlein, Erwin (see Strouse, Norman) (Box OS17)
  - Ulrich, Einer, circa 1967-1969 (Box OS17)
  - Umemoto, T. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS17)
  - Vanasin, Charuvarn, circa 1985 (Box OS17)
  - Van den Eynnde, Alain, circa 1985 (Box OS17)
  - Van Etten, Floyd, 1965 (Box OS17)
  - Van Stom, Andre, 1970s-1980 (Box OS17)
  - Velmans, Loet A., undated (Box OS17)
  - Venkatesh Rao, N. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS17)
  - Veres, Tom, circa 1960s (Box OS17)
  - Vincent, James, 1995 (Box OS17)
  - Volbach, Jochen, 1987 (Box OS17)
  - Volpi, Larry, 1993 (Box OS17)
  - von Thuna, Baron (see Resor, Stanley) (Box OS17)
  - Waldo, Ruth, circa 1940s-1962 (Box OS17)
  - Walker, Neil, 1972 (Box OS17)
  - Walker, Reginald (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS17)
  - Wallis, Gordon T., circa early 1980s (Box OS17)
  - Wallrapp, Yustin, 1977 (Box OS17)
  - Walshe, Elwyn R. (Wyn), 1979-1980 (Box OS17)
  - Walter, undated (Box OS17)
  - Walters, Larry, 1977 (Box OS17)
  - Walthius, George, 1972 (Box OS17)
  - Ward, Kenneth, undated (Box OS17)
  - Warhol, Andy (see Marshall, Dan) (Box OS17)
  - Warrier, M.R. (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS17)
  - Wason, Thomas, 1960s (Box OS17)
  - Waters, David, 1974 (Box OS17)
  - Watson, Art, 1963-1970s (Box OS17)
  - Watson, Tee, undated (Box OS17)
  - Watts, Andrew MacLean (see Thompson, Donald) (Box OS17)
  - Webster, Juan (Jack) G.O. (see also: Offices: Chile), circa 1950s-1960s (Box OS17)
  - Weekes, Allan, circa 1961, 1968 (Box OS17)
  - Weith, Warren, undated (Box OS17)
  - Wells, John, 1970s-1980s (Box OS17)
  - Wells, Lisa, circa 1996 (Box OS17)
  - Welty, Robert W., circa 1960s (Box OS17)
  - Wentzel, Roland T., 1957 (Box OS17)
  - Werle, Chuck, 1977 (Box OS17)
  - Wessell, Wessell, circa 1950 (Box OS17)
  - Wharton, Clifton, R. (see Johnston, G. Donald) (Box OS17)
  - White, Jeff, 1980s (Box OS17)
  - White, Robert F., circa 1940s-1960s (Box OS17)
  - White, William (see Johnston, G. Donald) (Box OS17)
  - Whiteside, Henry, 1960s (Box OS17)
  - Wierum, Thorn, 1976, late 1980s (Box OS17)
  - Wilken, David, circa 1985 (Box OS17)
  - Wilkes, D., undated (Box OS17)
  - Will, Joane Marie, 1973, late 1970s (Box OS17)
  - Williams, Eddie (see Sutton, Thomas) (Box OS17)
  - Willie, John, 1972 (Box OS17)
  - Wilson, Edward B. (Ted) (see also: Corporate Events; Offices: New York; Events: Farewell to Wilson, Edward B.; Retirements), circa 1960s-1970s (Box OS17)
  - Wilson, Edward G., circa 1950s-1980s, (1-3 of 12 folders) (Box OS17)
  - Wilson, Edward G. (continued), circa 1950s-1980s, (4-12 of 12 folders) (Box OS18)
  - Wilson, Jane (see Wilson, Edward G.) (Box OS18)
  - Wohl, Jack, circa 1965 (Box OS18)
  - Wolf, Samuel, circa 1974 (Box OS18)
  - Wood, William, 1971 (Box OS18)
  - Woodell, Shirley F. (Woody), 1955, 1984 (Box OS18)
  - Wright, Anne, circa 1950s-1960s (Box OS18)
  - Yalowitz, Ed, 1965 (Box OS18)
  - [Young, Andrew (see Johnston, G. Donald) (Box OS18)
  - [Young, Coleman (see Hieber, Marilyn) (Box OS18)
  - Young, James Webb, 1926-1960s, (3 folders) (Box OS18)
  - Yunich, David L., undated (Box OS18)
  - Yuspeh, Sonia E., 1977-1981 (Box OS18)
  - Zach, Bob, circa 1996 (Box OS18)
  - Zamparo, Roger, 1977 (Box OS18)
  - Zarry, Peter T., circa 1965-1967 (Box OS18)
  - Ziegler, Ron, 1968 (Box OS18)
  - Unidentified group and other photographs (Box OS18)
  - Unidentified portraits
    - JWT Owls baseball team, undated (Box OS18)
    - Meeting/Action photograph, 1970s (Box OS18)
    - [Poster of employees in the military, 1940s: See Oversized Materials] (Box OS18)
    - Receptions, (2 folders) (Box OS18)
    - Staff retreats, undated (Box OS18)
    - Telephone operators, circa 1971 (Box OS18)
    - Three men in pose, undated (Box OS18)
    - Training session, undated (Box OS18)
- Negatives, 1880s-1986 and undated, (11 boxes)
  Consists of negatives; where prints are known to exist, that fact is noted, otherwise cross-reference to print images has primarily been made beginning with the photographs, where the existence of corresponding negatives has been noted where known. Arranged according to the overall arrangement scheme for the photographs.
  - Corporate Events
    - New York Office, moving day, 1976 (Box NE1)
  - Advertisements (Domestic)